<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Administration &#8211; Partners HealthCare International</title>
	<atom:link href="http://phc-international.muellerarchive.com/staff-category/administration/feed" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://phc-international.muellerarchive.com/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2020 15:42:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.8.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>http://phc-international.muellerarchive.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/11/cropped-p-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Administration &#8211; Partners HealthCare International</title>
	<link>http://phc-international.muellerarchive.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Lauren Williams, RN, DM</title>
		<link>http://phc-international.muellerarchive.com/staff/lauren-williams-rn-dm</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nicole Motta]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2020 15:40:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://phc-international.muellerarchive.com/?post_type=staff&#038;p=2739</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Lauren Williams serves as the Director, Global Health, Hospital Operations Planning at Partners HealthCare International (PHI) advising in the areas of organizational operations, quality and patient safety, clinical program planning, workforce development, nursing, leadership development and academic planning. In collaboration with a variety of experts across the Partners HealthCare System, Dr. Williams’ focus is the&#8230;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://phc-international.muellerarchive.com/staff/lauren-williams-rn-dm">Lauren Williams, RN, DM</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://phc-international.muellerarchive.com/">Partners HealthCare International</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Lauren Williams serves as the Director, Global Health, Hospital Operations Planning at Partners HealthCare International (PHI) advising in the areas of organizational operations, quality and patient safety, clinical program planning, workforce development, nursing, leadership development and academic planning.</p>
<p>In collaboration with a variety of experts across the Partners HealthCare System, Dr. Williams’ focus is the design and development of organizations that achieve their mission and advance a distinctive vision. She works with organizational and clinical leaders to develop high quality and efficient programs while also creating healing, caring, and satisfying environments for those served and for caregivers.</p>
<p>Dr. Williams has extensive experience working in both the community and academic settings as a senior leader, professional development specialist, and a clinician. Prior to joining PHI, she was the Vice President of Patient Care Services/CNO at Yale New Haven Health’s Lawrence + Memorial Hospital and Westerly Hospital.</p>
<p>Dr. Williams became a Registered Nurse after graduating from the Peter Bent Brigham Hospital School of Nursing (Boston, MA). In addition, she received a Bachelor of Science from Salve Regina University (Newport, RI); a Master of Science in the Administration of Nursing Services from Boston University (Boston, MA); and a Doctor of Management awarded by Case Western Reserve University (Cleveland, OH). She holds a certificate in advanced graduate studies in Global Health Nursing from the Massachusetts General Hospital Institute of Health Professions. In 2017, she was selected to participate in the Global Nursing Leadership Institute (Geneva, Switzerland).</p>
<p>Dr. Williams has been a speaker at local, national, and international conferences most often describing replicable inter-professional strategies for reducing patient harm, medically induced trauma, developing organizational trust and justice, and applying design concepts to leadership practice.</p>
<p>She is an active member of the American Organization of Nurse Leaders; Sigma Theta Tau International Honor Society of Nursing, past president of the Connecticut Organization of Nurse Executives; past regional Board member of the Organization of Nurse Leaders MA, RI, NH, CT and VT; past chairperson of the Connecticut Hospital Association Patient Care Executive Group; and the Sigma Theta Tau International Honor Society of Nurses. In addition, she has held tenure track academic positions at Providence College (Providence, RI) and Suffolk University’s Sawyer School of Management (Boston, MA) where she continues to teach. Dr. Williams holds a faculty appointment in the University of California San Francisco’s School of Nursing where she teaches inter-professional graduate courses in healthcare administration and leadership.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://phc-international.muellerarchive.com/staff/lauren-williams-rn-dm">Lauren Williams, RN, DM</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://phc-international.muellerarchive.com/">Partners HealthCare International</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
