<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Leadership &#8211; Partners HealthCare International</title>
	<atom:link href="http://phc-international.muellerarchive.com/staff-category/leadership/feed" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://phc-international.muellerarchive.com/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 14:51:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.8.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>http://phc-international.muellerarchive.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/11/cropped-p-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Leadership &#8211; Partners HealthCare International</title>
	<link>http://phc-international.muellerarchive.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Thomas Aretz, MD</title>
		<link>http://phc-international.muellerarchive.com/staff/thomas-aretz</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ts_admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2017 20:56:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://partnersintl.wpengine.com/staff/betsy-brown-copy</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>H. Thomas Aretz, MD, is a member of Partners HealthCare International (PHI)’s senior management team focusing largely on academic programs and institutions, such as universities, medical schools and academic medical centers. A native of Germany, Dr. Aretz has been in the academic practice of cardiovascular pathology since 1981. He was the course director of a&#8230;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://phc-international.muellerarchive.com/staff/thomas-aretz">Thomas Aretz, MD</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://phc-international.muellerarchive.com/">Partners HealthCare International</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>H. Thomas Aretz, MD, is a member of Partners HealthCare International (PHI)’s senior management team focusing largely on academic programs and institutions, such as universities, medical schools and academic medical centers.</p>
<p>A native of Germany, Dr. Aretz has been in the academic practice of cardiovascular pathology since 1981. He was the course director of a major integrated medical school course at Harvard from 1992 to 2005. He is a Program Director for the Harvard Macy Institute, and has been involved in international programs since 1996. He holds a clinical appointment at the Massachusetts General Hospital (MGH), where he completed his post-doctoral training. He has served on many academic and hospital (IRB chairman) committees and industrial boards, and is the co-founder of three medical technology companies. He received his medical degree from Harvard Medical School and is certified in anatomic and clinical pathology by the American Board of Pathology.</p>
<p>Dr. Aretz has lectured and published extensively and has received multiple teaching awards at Harvard Medical School and MGH. He has also won recognition for his efforts to improve medical education around the world through intra-institutional collaborations. In 2006 he was named an “Ehrenbürger” (honorary citizen) of the Ludwig Maximilians University in Munich for his contributions to the long-standing then-PHMI-LMU alliance. In 2007, he was recognized with a MILES Award (Mentoring, Innovation, and Leadership in Educational Scholarship), given by the Yong Loo Lin School of Medicine at the National University of Singapore, for outstanding contributions to the advancement of global medical education and academic medicine.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://phc-international.muellerarchive.com/staff/thomas-aretz">Thomas Aretz, MD</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://phc-international.muellerarchive.com/">Partners HealthCare International</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Chris Coburn</title>
		<link>http://phc-international.muellerarchive.com/staff/chris-coburn</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ts_admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2015 15:27:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://phc-international.muellerarchive.com/staff/chris-coburn</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Chris Coburn is Chief Innovation Officer, Partners HealthCare System and President, Partners HealthCare International. Partners consists of Harvard University affiliates Brigham and Women’s Hospital, Massachusetts General Hospital, Massachusetts Eye and Ear, and McLean Hospital. Partners is the nation’s largest academic research enterprise with over $13 billion in annual revenue, 1.5 million patient visits and $1.7&#8230;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://phc-international.muellerarchive.com/staff/chris-coburn">Chris Coburn</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://phc-international.muellerarchive.com/">Partners HealthCare International</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Chris Coburn is Chief Innovation Officer, Partners HealthCare System and President, Partners HealthCare International. Partners consists of Harvard University affiliates Brigham and Women’s Hospital, Massachusetts General Hospital, Massachusetts Eye and Ear, and McLean Hospital. Partners is the nation’s largest academic research enterprise with over $13 billion in annual revenue, 1.5 million patient visits and $1.7 billion in research expenditures. It also has a managed care organization, out-patient facilities and community hospitals. Partners 6200 faculty are appointed at Harvard Medical School.</p>
<p>Mr. Coburn leads a team of more than 125 tasked with the worldwide commercial application of the unique capabilities and discoveries of all Partners’ 74,000 employees. His unit’s business development responsibilities include investing, company creation, international consulting, innovation management, industry collaborations, and licensing. Commercialization revenue exceeds $130 million annually and more than 225 companies have been spun-off from Partners in the last decade. Large-scale industry collaborations have been established in areas such as AI and drug development. Provider strategy and operational consulting has been delivered to clients in nearly 40 countries. His group also manages a nearly $200 million venture fund.</p>
<p>Prior to joining Partners, Mr. Coburn was founding director of Cleveland Clinic Innovations and served for 13 years as its executive leader. During his tenure Cleveland Clinic spun off 57 companies that raised more than $700 million in equity financing. There were none before Coburn’s arrival. His team also managed an innovation alliance network in which Cleveland Clinic directly supported technology commercialization for healthcare systems throughout the United States.</p>
<p>Mr. Coburn has been a member of numerous corporate and community boards including Explorys (acquired by IBM), Autonomic Technologies, and the U.S. Enrichment Corporation (NYSE:USU).</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://phc-international.muellerarchive.com/staff/chris-coburn">Chris Coburn</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://phc-international.muellerarchive.com/">Partners HealthCare International</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Trung Do</title>
		<link>http://phc-international.muellerarchive.com/staff/trung-do</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ts_admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2015 15:27:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://phc-international.muellerarchive.com/staff/trung-do</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Trung is Vice President of Business Development at Partners HealthCare, where he has overall responsibility leading Partners efforts to grow its commercial and international portfolios. Trung’s background includes more than fifteen years experience in strategy, business development, management consulting, and operations. Prior to Partners, he served as the Director of Operations at PharMetrics, a venture-backed&#8230;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://phc-international.muellerarchive.com/staff/trung-do">Trung Do</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://phc-international.muellerarchive.com/">Partners HealthCare International</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Trung is Vice President of Business Development at Partners HealthCare, where he has overall responsibility leading Partners efforts to grow its commercial and international portfolios. Trung’s background includes more than fifteen years experience in strategy, business development, management consulting, and operations. Prior to Partners, he served as the Director of Operations at PharMetrics, a venture-backed start-up providing healthcare market insights to the pharmaceutical, biotech, medical device, and health plan sectors of the market. He began his career in healthcare and life sciences as a consultant with Arthur Andersen and Boston Biomedical Consultants. He served as the President of GeneInsight, Inc., a company of Partners HealthCare, before it was acquired by Sunquest Information Systems. He currently serves as a member of the Clinical Translational Research and Innovation Centre’s (C-TRIC) international advisory board. Trung holds an MBA and MA from Boston University and BS from University of California at Irvine.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://phc-international.muellerarchive.com/staff/trung-do">Trung Do</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://phc-international.muellerarchive.com/">Partners HealthCare International</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
