<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Beth Mollineaux &#8211; Partners HealthCare International</title>
	<atom:link href="http://phc-international.muellerarchive.com/author/partners-innovation/feed" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://phc-international.muellerarchive.com/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Mar 2018 17:22:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.8.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>http://phc-international.muellerarchive.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/11/cropped-p-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Beth Mollineaux &#8211; Partners HealthCare International</title>
	<link>http://phc-international.muellerarchive.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>New Stroke Rehab Unit Opens In Malta Through Hard Work Of PHS Experts</title>
		<link>http://phc-international.muellerarchive.com/news/new-stroke-rehab-unit-opens-malta-hard-work-phs-experts</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Beth Mollineaux]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2017 11:58:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[General News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://phc-international.muellerarchive.com/?p=2593</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>It’s difficult enough to coordinate patient care across departments or hospitals, but what happens when the care process takes place on two different islands? That was just one of the challenges tackled by an interdisciplinary team from Spaulding Rehabilitation Network (SRN) and Partners HealthCare International (PHI) that recently traveled to the VGH Karin Grech Hospital&#8230;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://phc-international.muellerarchive.com/news/new-stroke-rehab-unit-opens-malta-hard-work-phs-experts">New Stroke Rehab Unit Opens In Malta Through Hard Work Of PHS Experts</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://phc-international.muellerarchive.com/">Partners HealthCare International</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>It’s difficult enough to coordinate patient care across departments or hospitals, but what happens when the care process takes place on two different islands?</p>
<p>That was just one of the challenges tackled by an interdisciplinary team from Spaulding Rehabilitation Network (SRN) and Partners HealthCare International (PHI) that recently traveled to the VGH Karin Grech Hospital (KGH) in Malta for the opening of a newly renovated, 28-bed stroke rehabilitation unit.</p>
<p>Part of the Vitals Global Healthcare (VGH) network, the unit’s launch is the first step in a comprehensive plan to improve the care for stroke patients and one of a series of initiatives taking place as part of a multiyear agreement between PHI and VGH, explains Betsy Cox, Director of Global Nursing Programs for PHI.</p>
<p>Other initiatives include programs to improve quality and safety, strengthen the program infrastructure, information technology, nursing, and clinical rehabilitation care, Cox says. “We are working on quality and safety with them, moving toward international accreditation, and working closely with nursing leadership development.”</p>
<p>Malta is an archipelago in the Mediterranean Sea that includes the larger island of Malta and the smaller island of Gozo and sparsely populated island of Comino. It is located about 50 miles south of Italy. Approximately 700 patients on the two islands suffer strokes each year. Stroke patients receive care on either island and the goal is to define a stroke pathway across the continuum of care for patients across Gozo and Malta to provide the right level of care at the right time to improve outcomes, satisfaction and efficiency.</p>
<p>“In Malta patients who have suffered a stroke are admitted to Mater Dei Hospital for acute care management. What the patient needs next is dedicated rehabilitation care to start relearning skills,” explained Stephen Zammit, MD, CEO of VGH’s Karin Grech Hospital. “Through our collaboration with Partners and Spaulding Rehabilitation Network we are now able to offer our patients this specialized rehabilitation.”</p>
<p>The new rehabilitation unit at Karin Grech Hospital is located within an existing area of the hospital. The newly opened unit was refurbished to focus exclusively on stroke rehabilitation and features an updated gymnasium and new technologies to assist in the recovery process.</p>
<p>In addition to the facility updates, the teams collaborated on new strategies for educating staff, scheduling patients, conducting case discussions, setting goals for patients, involving families in the care process, and preparing for the next transition of care.</p>
<p>“We’ve delivered some of the work and we will continue to work with KGH remotely as they implement these changes and review targeted performance measures to see how well they are improving care in stroke rehabilitation,” Cox explains.</p>
<p>Cox was quick to highlight the critical role played by the team from SRN, which included physicians, nurses, speech language pathologists, physical therapists, and occupational therapists. “They worked hand in hand, shoulder to shoulder to help our colleagues in Malta through this process.”</p>
<p>PHI, the international arm of Partners HealthCare, has been collaborating with hospitals and health care organizations across the globe for more than two decades. The PHI team merged with Partners Innovation in 2016. The unique model of international collaboration is based on a two-way exchange of ideas rather than exporting a single approach or methodology. In this case, the goal was not for VGH to do everything the same way that the Spaulding team does it, but to combine global best practices with local considerations and identify solutions that work best for this country.</p>
<p>While the advisory teams from Partners have a lot to offer their international colleagues, there is much to gain as well.</p>
<p>“You always learn how our international colleagues do things differently,” Cox says. “Maybe they are using protocols from the European Union or have different cultural practices. You are always extracting ideas from each other and being able to say, ‘Hey, I didn’t think about it that way—we might be able to implement that.’”</p>
<p>For Cox, one of the most gratifying parts of the collaboration is watching the spirit of teamwork develop as the project moves along, not only between the PHI/Spaulding and VGH teams but within VGH as well.</p>
<p>“I think it’s always extremely rewarding to see how these teams that have come from across the globe, and there locally, across two islands, are able to work together and have this impact when so many of them didn’t even know each other beforehand.”</p>
<p>“They come from the same hospital or the same country. Now, not only do they know each other, but they are standardizing care in a way that will have an impact on the patient.”</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://phc-international.muellerarchive.com/news/new-stroke-rehab-unit-opens-malta-hard-work-phs-experts">New Stroke Rehab Unit Opens In Malta Through Hard Work Of PHS Experts</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://phc-international.muellerarchive.com/">Partners HealthCare International</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bermuda Cancer and Health Centre and Dana Farber/Brigham and Women&#8217;s Cancer Center to Partner</title>
		<link>http://phc-international.muellerarchive.com/press-releases/bermuda-cancer-health-centre</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Beth Mollineaux]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2015 17:42:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Releases]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://partnersintl.wpengine.com/?p=2465</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bermuda Cancer and Health Centre and Dana Farber/Brigham and Women's Cancer Center Announce Plans to Partner on the Development of a Radiotherapy Program Hamilton, Bermuda – September 17, 2015 -- Bermuda Cancer and Health Centre and Dana-Farber/Brigham and Women’s Cancer Center (DF/BWCC) announce today the signing of a Memorandum of Understanding to collaborate on the&#8230;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://phc-international.muellerarchive.com/press-releases/bermuda-cancer-health-centre">Bermuda Cancer and Health Centre and Dana Farber/Brigham and Women&#8217;s Cancer Center to Partner</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://phc-international.muellerarchive.com/">Partners HealthCare International</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="fl-builder-content fl-builder-content-2465 fl-builder-content-primary fl-builder-global-templates-locked" data-post-id="2465"><div class="fl-row fl-row-fixed-width fl-row-bg-none fl-node-59778323aae8a" data-node="59778323aae8a">
	<div class="fl-row-content-wrap">
								<div class="fl-row-content fl-row-fixed-width fl-node-content">
		
<div class="fl-col-group fl-node-59778323abcff" data-node="59778323abcff">
			<div class="fl-col fl-node-59778323abda0" data-node="59778323abda0">
	<div class="fl-col-content fl-node-content">
	<div class="fl-module fl-module-rich-text fl-node-59778323adecb" data-node="59778323adecb">
	<div class="fl-module-content fl-node-content">
		<div class="fl-rich-text">
	<h5>Bermuda Cancer and Health Centre and Dana Farber/Brigham and Women's Cancer Center Announce Plans to Partner on the Development of a Radiotherapy Program</h5>
<p>Hamilton, Bermuda – September 17, 2015 -- Bermuda Cancer and Health Centre and <a href="http://www.brighamandwomens.org/bwhcancer/default.aspx" target="blank">Dana-Farber/Brigham and Women’s Cancer Center</a> (DF/BWCC) announce today the signing of a Memorandum of Understanding to collaborate on the development of a radiotherapy program.</p>
<p>“This is the next very important phase in developing radiation therapy plans for the local treatment of cancer patients in Bermuda. Bermuda Cancer and Health Centre recognizes how crucial it is to establish collaborative clinical affiliations with overseas cancer centers so that we will safely and effectively provide the highest quality level of cancer care locally,” says Bermuda Cancer and Health Centre, Executive Director, Tara Soares.</p>
<p>Experts from DF/BWCC will advise Bermuda on issues related to the development of the program, including design of a facility, the creation of clinical radiation oncology policies, procedures and safety protocols and the development of a training and education program. Additionally, BWH will work with Bermuda Cancer and Health Centre to explore the opportunity to participate in research opportunities as well as a telemedicine program.</p>
<p>“We are excited to partner with Bermuda Cancer and Health Centre to expand the radiation oncology services available to patients in Bermuda. We share a commitment to providing patient and family-centered care, and through this partnership, most patients who require radiation therapy will no longer need to travel off the island to receive high quality care,” said <a href="http://physiciandirectory.brighamandwomens.org/Details/12752?LastName=Haas-Kogan&amp;Index=1" target="blank">Daphne Haas-Kogan, MD</a>, chair, Department of Radiation Oncology, Dana-Farber/Brigham and Women’s Cancer Center and professor at Harvard Medical School.</p>
<p>Partners HealthCare International® (PHI), the international arm of Partners HealthCare, and its member hospitals have worked in collaboration with the Bermuda Cancer and Health Centre, the Bermuda Hospitals Board, as well as Bermuda’s insurance and physician providers to elevate local health care services for nearly 15-years. “The impact of an expanded cancer care program will not only address escalating health care costs for the country, it will also make care more efficient and less stressful for Bermudians. The partnership between DF/BWCC and the Bermuda Cancer and Health Centre marks another important milestone in the work we do on the island,” said Dr. Gilbert H. Mudge, CEO for PHI.</p>
<p>Chairman of Bermuda Cancer and Health Centre’s Board of Directors, Glen Gibbons states, “Dana Farber / Brigham and Women’s Cancer Centre is ranked the 4th Best Hospital for Adult Cancer treatment in the USA, according to the US News Best Hospitals Rankings for 2015. We are proud to partner with them to provide our patients in Bermuda access to the latest therapies at a comprehensive radiation treatment facility with a mission of providing cancer treatment to everyone who needs it, regardless of their ability to pay.”</p>
<h5>Bermuda Cancer and Health</h5>
<p>Bermuda Cancer and Health Centre is an American College of Radiology (ACR) designated Breast Imaging Centre of Excellence and a registered charity number #70. Clinical services include Digital Mammography, Ultrasound, Breast Biopsy and Bone Densitometry. With two digital mammography suites, the Centre performs over 9000 mammograms per year. Bermuda Cancer and Health Centre strongly believe that health screenings, such as mammograms and ultrasound should be available to everyone regardless of insurance coverage or ability to pay. Providing a specialist approach to patient care, Bermuda Cancer and Health Centre has, flexible hours (including after work and Saturday appointments), a convenient location, and lots of free parking. For more information: <a href="http://www.cancer.bm/" target="blank">www.cancer.bm</a>. For more information about Bermuda Cancer and Health Centre visit our website <a href="http://www.cancer.bm/" target="blank">www.chc.bm</a> or call 236-1001.</p>
<h5>Dana-Farber/Brigham and Women’s Cancer Care</h5>
<p>Dana-Farber/Brigham and Women’s Cancer Center (DF/BWCC) offers the combined strengths of two world-renowned leaders in cancer treatment and research to provide the most innovative treatment for adults challenged with cancer. It is consistently the top ranked cancer center in New England by US News and World Report. Dana-Farber Cancer Institute and Brigham and Women’s Hospital are founding members of Dana-Farber/Harvard Cancer Center, the nation’s largest research program and an NCI-designated Comprehensive Cancer Center. Our team of clinical specialists and researchers are committed to conquering cancer by developing new ways to prevent, screen for, and treat the disease. Brigham and Women’s Hospital is a founding member of Partners HealthCare and a teaching hospital at Harvard Medical School.</p>
</div>
	</div>
</div>
	</div>
</div>
	</div>

<div class="fl-col-group fl-node-598b07c2d3905" data-node="598b07c2d3905">
			<div class="fl-col fl-node-598b07c2d39ae" data-node="598b07c2d39ae">
	<div class="fl-col-content fl-node-content">
	<div class="fl-module fl-module-separator fl-node-598b07c2d386c" data-node="598b07c2d386c">
	<div class="fl-module-content fl-node-content">
		<div class="fl-separator"></div>
	</div>
</div>
	</div>
</div>
	</div>

<div class="fl-col-group fl-node-598b07ab69024" data-node="598b07ab69024">
			<div class="fl-col fl-node-598b07ab690ef" data-node="598b07ab690ef">
	<div class="fl-col-content fl-node-content">
	<div class="fl-module fl-module-rich-text fl-node-598b07ab68f9e" data-node="598b07ab68f9e">
	<div class="fl-module-content fl-node-content">
		<div class="fl-rich-text">
	<p><a href="/media-center"><strong>All Posts</strong></a></p>
</div>
	</div>
</div>
	</div>
</div>
	</div>
		</div>
	</div>
</div>
</div><div class="uabb-js-breakpoint" style="display: none;"></div><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://phc-international.muellerarchive.com/press-releases/bermuda-cancer-health-centre">Bermuda Cancer and Health Centre and Dana Farber/Brigham and Women&#8217;s Cancer Center to Partner</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://phc-international.muellerarchive.com/">Partners HealthCare International</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Partners HealthCare Launches Year-long Global Initiative in Support of International Nurses Day 2015</title>
		<link>http://phc-international.muellerarchive.com/press-releases/international-nurses-day</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Beth Mollineaux]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 May 2015 17:54:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Releases]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://partnersintl.wpengine.com/press-releases/jiahui-international-hospital-copy</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Boston, MA - May 14, 2015 -- In recognition of International Nurses Day, Partners HealthCare International® (PHI) this week announced a year-long global initiative that will focus on nurses as a force for change in improving health care quality, efficiency, education, and work environment. "Nurses represent the largest percent of our global healthcare workforce and&#8230;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://phc-international.muellerarchive.com/press-releases/international-nurses-day">Partners HealthCare Launches Year-long Global Initiative in Support of International Nurses Day 2015</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://phc-international.muellerarchive.com/">Partners HealthCare International</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="fl-builder-content fl-builder-content-2467 fl-builder-content-primary fl-builder-global-templates-locked" data-post-id="2467"><div class="fl-row fl-row-fixed-width fl-row-bg-none fl-node-59778323aae8a" data-node="59778323aae8a">
	<div class="fl-row-content-wrap">
								<div class="fl-row-content fl-row-fixed-width fl-node-content">
		
<div class="fl-col-group fl-node-59778323abcff" data-node="59778323abcff">
			<div class="fl-col fl-node-59778323abda0" data-node="59778323abda0">
	<div class="fl-col-content fl-node-content">
	<div class="fl-module fl-module-rich-text fl-node-59778323adecb" data-node="59778323adecb">
	<div class="fl-module-content fl-node-content">
		<div class="fl-rich-text">
	<p>Boston, MA - May 14, 2015 -- In recognition of International Nurses Day, Partners HealthCare International® (PHI) this week announced a year-long global initiative that will focus on nurses as a force for change in improving health care quality, efficiency, education, and work environment. "Nurses represent the largest percent of our global healthcare workforce and their ability to lead, influence and impact improvements cannot be underestimated," said Elizabeth Brown, Director of Nursing and Global Programs for PHI. This year's theme for International Nurses Day is "Nurses Force for Change: Care Effective, Cost Effective," and PHI is kicking off activities by launching a digital library (<a href="http://www.partners.org/international/News-And-Perspectives/Events/International-Nurses-Day.aspx" target="blank">www.partners.org/international/forceforchange2015</a>) that highlights global partnerships, projects and initiatives driven by the nurses from Partners HealthCare member hospitals, including Brigham and Women's Hospital, Massachusetts General Hospital, and the network's affiliated community hospitals and departments.</p>
<p>According to the International Council of Nurses (ICN), sponsors of International Nurses Day, "nurses are part of the solution to achieve better health for all in a care effective, cost effective way." The World Health Organization (WHO) reports the average number of nurses per population across the world is estimated to be 29 for every 10,000 people, yet this rate differs drastically across countries and regions, challenging the safe, effective delivery of patient care. Lower nurse staffing, increased workloads, and unstable nursing unit environments are linked to negative patient outcomes ranging from falls to medication errors, [For more on worldwide nursing trends, see <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HU7RHciqa-I" target="blank">Global Nursing by the Numbers</a>]. As a result, nurses from the bedside to the boardroom are working to make a positive impact to improve how nurses are educated and how care is delivered.</p>
<p>As part of the year-long initiative, Partners is demonstrating how nurses across the world are embracing this year's theme. "Nurses globally are working to strengthen competencies as health care delivery becomes more complex, are being recognized as a valued member of the care team, and are dedicated to improving working conditions and the quality of care and patient safety," said Brown.</p>
<p>For nearly 20 years PHI has had the opportunity to partner with global health care organizations for bilateral sharing of best practices to improve the critical skills of their nurses with the goal of providing safe, high-quality patient care. In its work with clients, PHI engages the vast expertise and knowledge available throughout the Partners nursing community. "We invite the global nursing community to visit the digital library throughout the year and see how nurses are working to help innovate and shape the future of nursing," said Brown.</p>
<h5>About Partners HealthCare International</h5>
<p>Partners HealthCare International (PHI) is the global arm of Partners HealthCare, one of the leading not-for-profit health care systems in the U.S. Founded in 1997, PHI is dedicated to advancing the Partners HealthCare mission worldwide through collaborations and partnerships designed to expand a global client's capacity to deliver high quality health care. Partners was founded in 1994 by Brigham and Women's Hospital and Massachusetts General Hospital, the two oldest and largest teaching hospitals of Harvard Medical School, and includes community and specialty hospitals, a managed care organization, a physician network, community health centers, home care and other health-related entities. Partners' five top-ranked hospitals comprise part of the health care system, and all are recognized by the 2014 - 2015 U.S. News and World Report. To learn more about PHI and how we are extending the capabilities of healthcare systems worldwide, visit www.partners.org/international.</p>
<p>For more information contact:<br />
Stephanie Adams, PHI Marketing &amp; Communications, 011-617-535-6478, E-mail: <a href="mailto:sadams9@partners.org">sadams9@partners.org</a></p>
</div>
	</div>
</div>
	</div>
</div>
	</div>

<div class="fl-col-group fl-node-598b081357a0f" data-node="598b081357a0f">
			<div class="fl-col fl-node-598b081357aba" data-node="598b081357aba">
	<div class="fl-col-content fl-node-content">
	<div class="fl-module fl-module-separator fl-node-598b081357996" data-node="598b081357996">
	<div class="fl-module-content fl-node-content">
		<div class="fl-separator"></div>
	</div>
</div>
	</div>
</div>
	</div>

<div class="fl-col-group fl-node-598b07fb41103" data-node="598b07fb41103">
			<div class="fl-col fl-node-598b07fb411fd" data-node="598b07fb411fd">
	<div class="fl-col-content fl-node-content">
	<div class="fl-module fl-module-rich-text fl-node-598b07fb4105c" data-node="598b07fb4105c">
	<div class="fl-module-content fl-node-content">
		<div class="fl-rich-text">
	<p><a href="/media-center"><strong>All Posts</strong></a></p>
</div>
	</div>
</div>
	</div>
</div>
	</div>
		</div>
	</div>
</div>
</div><div class="uabb-js-breakpoint" style="display: none;"></div><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://phc-international.muellerarchive.com/press-releases/international-nurses-day">Partners HealthCare Launches Year-long Global Initiative in Support of International Nurses Day 2015</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://phc-international.muellerarchive.com/">Partners HealthCare International</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>PHI and China Creation Holding Group Partner to Develop New International Standard Hospital</title>
		<link>http://phc-international.muellerarchive.com/press-releases/phi-and-china-creation-holding-group</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Beth Mollineaux]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2015 18:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Releases]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://partnersintl.wpengine.com/press-releases/global-initiative-for-international-nurses-day-copy</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Chongqing, China - March 30, 2015 -- Partners HealthCare International (PHI)® today announced it signed an agreement with the China Creation Holding Group Company (CCHG) to advance the development of a new international standard hospital in Chongqing, China. For more than a decade PHI has collaborated with like-minded organizations to advance the broad healthcare capabilities&#8230;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://phc-international.muellerarchive.com/press-releases/phi-and-china-creation-holding-group">PHI and China Creation Holding Group Partner to Develop New International Standard Hospital</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://phc-international.muellerarchive.com/">Partners HealthCare International</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="fl-builder-content fl-builder-content-2469 fl-builder-content-primary fl-builder-global-templates-locked" data-post-id="2469"><div class="fl-row fl-row-fixed-width fl-row-bg-none fl-node-59778323aae8a" data-node="59778323aae8a">
	<div class="fl-row-content-wrap">
								<div class="fl-row-content fl-row-fixed-width fl-node-content">
		
<div class="fl-col-group fl-node-59778323abcff" data-node="59778323abcff">
			<div class="fl-col fl-node-59778323abda0" data-node="59778323abda0">
	<div class="fl-col-content fl-node-content">
	<div class="fl-module fl-module-rich-text fl-node-59778323adecb" data-node="59778323adecb">
	<div class="fl-module-content fl-node-content">
		<div class="fl-rich-text">
	<p>Chongqing, China - March 30, 2015 -- Partners HealthCare International (PHI)® today announced it signed an agreement with the China Creation Holding Group Company (CCHG) to advance the development of a new international standard hospital in Chongqing, China.</p>
<p>For more than a decade PHI has collaborated with like-minded organizations to advance the broad healthcare capabilities of organizations in China. “Partners HealthCare International is committed to improving health care in China,” said <a href="http://www.partners.org/international/About/Staff-Members/Gilbert-Mudge.aspx" target="blank">Gilbert H. Mudge, M.D</a>., President and CEO of PHI. “We are pleased to partner with the China Creation Holding Group, an organization whose primary objective is to create a better China for its citizens. We look forward to working together to create an innovative, international model of health care.”</p>
<p>As part of the agreement with CCHG, PHI will initiate a strategic planning and assessment program utilizing a team with expertise in clinical program planning, healthcare facilities planning and design, healthcare management and operations, staff development, nursing education and project management, while also leveraging experts from Harvard Medical School and its affiliate Partners network hospitals.</p>
<h5>About China Creation Holding Group (CCHG)</h5>
<p>With a nationwide footprint specializing in urban design, China Creation Holding Group (CCHG) is a national professional urban operation enterprise with a background of international high-end financial resources, focusing on new city development. CCHG’s key projects are located in first and second tier cities, such as Beijing, Shanghai, Nanjing, Chongqing, Heifei and Suzhou, etc. CCHG integrates and introduces in global resources in fields of healthy living, ecological wisdom, culture creativity, education and business, so as to build a sustainable international new city which is ecological, wisdom livable and mixed.</p>
<h5>About Partners HealthCare International</h5>
<p>Partners HealthCare International (PHI) is the global arm of Partners HealthCare, one of the leading integrated healthcare systems in the United States. Founded in 1997, PHI is dedicated to advancing the Partners HealthCare mission worldwide through collaborations and partnerships designed to expand a global client’s capacity to deliver high quality health care. Partners was founded in 1994 by Brigham and Women’s Hospital and Massachusetts General Hospital, the two oldest and largest teaching hospitals of Harvard Medical School, and includes community and specialty hospitals, a managed care organization, a physician network, community health centers, home care and other health-related entities. Partners’ five top-ranked hospitals comprise part of the health care system, and all are recognized by the 2014 - 2015 U.S. News and World Report. To learn more about PHI and how we are extending the capabilities of healthcare systems in China, India, Japan, the Middle East, as well as our commitment to international markets beyond, please visit www.partners.org/international.</p>
</div>
	</div>
</div>
	</div>
</div>
	</div>

<div class="fl-col-group fl-node-598b08551fa18" data-node="598b08551fa18">
			<div class="fl-col fl-node-598b08551fabc" data-node="598b08551fabc">
	<div class="fl-col-content fl-node-content">
	<div class="fl-module fl-module-separator fl-node-598b08551f994" data-node="598b08551f994">
	<div class="fl-module-content fl-node-content">
		<div class="fl-separator"></div>
	</div>
</div>
	</div>
</div>
	</div>

<div class="fl-col-group fl-node-598b08307d5f0" data-node="598b08307d5f0">
			<div class="fl-col fl-node-598b08307d689" data-node="598b08307d689">
	<div class="fl-col-content fl-node-content">
	<div class="fl-module fl-module-rich-text fl-node-598b08307d578" data-node="598b08307d578">
	<div class="fl-module-content fl-node-content">
		<div class="fl-rich-text">
	<p><a href="/media-center"><strong>All Posts</strong></a></p>
</div>
	</div>
</div>
	</div>
</div>
	</div>
		</div>
	</div>
</div>
</div><div class="uabb-js-breakpoint" style="display: none;"></div><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://phc-international.muellerarchive.com/press-releases/phi-and-china-creation-holding-group">PHI and China Creation Holding Group Partner to Develop New International Standard Hospital</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://phc-international.muellerarchive.com/">Partners HealthCare International</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
